<?xml version="1.0"?>

<book>
<page type="picture">
<text> </text>
<location>contained:books/logo.png</location>
</page>

<page type="contents">
<text>Table of Contents</text>
<link>
 <text>Getting Started</text>
 <icon>TerritoryFlag</icon>
 <jump>1</jump>
</link>
<link>
 <text>Town Hall</text>
 <icon>townHall</icon>
 <jump>2</jump>
</link>
<link>
 <text>Territory Gems/Machines</text>
 <icon>ClaimTerritoryMachine</icon>
 <jump>3</jump>
</link>
<link>
 <text>Guilds</text>
 <jump>4</jump>
</link>
<link>
 <text>Occupational Classes</text>
 <jump>5</jump>
</link>
<link>
 <text>Perks</text>
 <jump>7</jump>
</link>
</page>

<page type="sectionpage">
<title>Territory Flag</title>
<text>This is an item usable only by team leaders. It allows you to start a single block of land as your territory, which you and your team members can later expand off of. There are no restrictions on where you can use this, as long as the block is not already owned by another team. The first time use of the flag is free, but subsequent uses require a steep amount of experience levels. </text>
</page>

<page type="crafting">
<text>Territory Flag</text>
<recipe>
 <name>TerritoryFlag</name>
 <size>three</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="sectionpage">
<title>Town Hall</title>
<text>This is an important block that every team should have. It enables the purchasing and managing of various things that will be essential for the growth and success of the players' town.

§lTerritory Purchasing:§r This tab allows you to spend experience levels in order to purchase items that will allow you to expand your team's territory, as well as take over other teams' territories, if you so desire.
</text>
</page>

<page type="crafting">
<text>Town Hall</text>
<recipe>
 <name>townHall</name>
 <size>two</size>
</recipe>
</page>

<page type="toolpage">
<title>Territory Gems</title>
<text>One-time use item that allows acquisition of a single extra block of territory… but it must be one that’s directly adjacent to the land your team already owns.

The Anti-gem is similar, except it allows you to remove a block of another (specific) team’s territory. It must be territory at the very edge/perimeter of that team’s land. Using one on your own territory refunds you experience levels.

Anti-gems drop when you kill
a player from another team.
</text>
<item>
 <text>Territory Gem</text>
 <icon>ItemClaimTerritory</icon>
</item>
<item>
 <text>Anti-Territory Gem</text>
 <icon>ItemRemoveTerritory</icon>
</item>
</page>

<page type="toolpage">
<title>Territory Machines</title>
<text>Unlimited use versions of the territory gems, that passively claim/remove land for you over time. You place the machine into the world, and it very slowly converts land within a small radius. The machines are confined to the same restrictions as the territory gems; for example, they can only claim land directly adjacent to your current territory.</text>
<item>
 <text>Territory Machine</text>
 <icon>ClaimTerritoryMachine</icon>
</item>
<item>
 <text>Anti-Territory Machine</text>
 <icon>RemoveTerritoryMachine</icon>
</item>
</page>

<page type="sectionpage">
<title>The Guilds</title>
<text>§lPress 'G' To Access The Guild Interface§r

Players can either join a guild or create their own. To create a guild, type in a unique name and select a color, then press the 'Create' button. The color you select will be used to highlight territories that you claim and highlight messages from your teammates. Guilds are allowed to have a maximum of 5 players on their teams and players are able to share a private chat log between each other. 
</text>
</page>

<page type="sectionpage">
<title>Guild Leader Pt.1</title>
<text>A leader of a guild can access three tabs in the guild interface: actions, teammates, and settings tabs.

§lActions Tab:§r This tab allows the leader to access diplomacy actions with other guilds on the server. The leader can also use it to set tasks for the guild members to accomplish to earn experience points for the town hall. Earning experience points will help the your guild purchase NPCs, items, and blocks from the town hall, which can give you advantages over other guilds.
</text>
</page>

<page type="sectionpage">
<title>Guild Leader Pt.2</title>
<text>§lTeam-mate Tab:§r This tab allows the leader to promote or demote a player in the guild, but the leader can also use it to kick a player out of the guild. If the guild leader demotes himself/herself, then another guild member who was promoted will become the guild leader.

§lSettings Tab:§r If the guild has not reached the maximum members limit, the leader can invite more players into the guild. The leader can also change the teams' name and color.    
</text>
</page>

<page type="sectionpage">
<title>Guild Player</title>
<text>Guild players have the option to leave the guild they are currently in. They can also accomplish tasks from the quest list that their leader posts to earn xp for their guild.
§lQuests: TODO§r
</text>
</page>

<page type="sectionpage">
<title>Occupational Classes Pt.1</title>
<text>§lPress 'P' To Access The Occupations Class Interface§r
You have the option of selecting a occupational class to specialize in: Collector, Builder, Cook, Wizard, and Warrior. By collecting specific items in the world, you can level up each one of the classes. You will be able to select a total of four different perks, but be wary of the perks you choose because when you select a perk, then you can only select that perks' child perks when leveling up again. It is highly recommended to select an occupation in order to gain advantages over other players and to give guild leaders an incentive to invite you into their guild.
</text>
</page>

<page type="sectionpage">
<title>Occupational Classes Pt.2</title>
<text>§lCollector Class:§r Mining ores and cutting down trees.
§lBuilder Class:§r
Crafting items for buildings, using redstone, pistons, and minecarts.
§lCook Class:§r Farming, cooking, and fishing.
§lWizard Class:§r 
Brewing potions, collecting neither world items, and enchanting items.
§lWarrior Class:§r Killing players or mobs.
Symbols:
(*) When Attacked by Player
(#) When Attacking Player/Mob
(~) When Mounted On A Horse
(!) When Item Held
</text>
</page>

<page type="sectionpage">
<title>Collector Class</title>
<text>§lPerks:§r
To Be Added
</text>
</page>

<page type="sectionpage">
<title>Builder Class</title>
<text>§lPerks:§r
To be Added
</text>
</page>

<page type="sectionpage">
<title>Cook Class</title>
<text>§lPerks:§r
(!) Wooden Hoe: -10% Damage 
(!) Stone Hoe: -15% Damage
Seeds: 2x Harvest
(!) Iron Hoe: +15% Attackl
(!) Fishing Rod: -15% Damage
(~) Apple: -10% Damage To Horse
Carrot: +10% Damage To Animals
(#) Golden Carrot: +10% Damage
Cookie: Restore Health
Golden Apple: +10% Damage To Horse
Cake: Restore Health
Salmon: Potion of Strength
Fish: Potion of Water Breathing
(!) Diamond Hoe: +25% Damage
(!) Golden Hoe: -25% Attack
</text>
</page>

<page type="sectionpage">
<title>Wizard Class</title>
<text>§lPerks:§r 
Bone: -10% Skeleton Damage
Enchantment Book: -10% Magical Damage
(#) Potion: Potion of Swiftness
Gun Powder: -10% Explosion Damage
Cauldron: -10% Damage By Witch
(*) Neither Brick: Potion of Fire Resistance
(#) Potion Stand: Poton of Strength
(#) Ender Pearl : Potion of Night Vision
(*) Ender Eye: Potion of Luck
(#) Fire: Potion of Invisibility
(*) Slime: Potion of Leaping
Spider: +10% Damage on Spiders
Ghast: +10% Damage on Ghast
Crystal: +10% Damage on Blaze
magma: -10% Fire Damage
</text>
</page>

<page type="sectionpage">
<title>Warrior Class</title>
<text>§lPerks:§r
Wooden Sword: +10% Attack
Leather Tunic: -10% Damage
Stone Sword: +10% Attack
(~) Iron Horse Armor: -20% Damage to Horse
Arrow: +5% Damage With Projectiles
(~) Diamond Horse Armor: -20% Damage To Horse
(~) Golden Horse Armor: -20% Damage To Horse
Diamond Sword: +10% Attack
Diamond Chest Plate: -10% Damage
Golden Sword: +10% Attack
Golden Chest Plate: -10% Damage
Iron Chest Plate: -10% Damage
Bow: +10% Range
(~) Saddle: +5% Speed To Horse
</text>
</page>

</book>